Finding Aid for Mary Hunt Papers 1976-2009
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs
  - Mainly with some earlier, 1998-1999
    - US 12 Allen to US127, October 1998 (Box 18)
    - Van Buren SP, Duck Lake SP, July 1999 (Box 18)